{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Lepage",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/homepage",
    "object": "http://www.robertlepage.com/",
    "human_readable": "Robert Lepage's homepage is http://www.robertlepage.com/",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.946074903011322,
            "question": "Is there a website dedicated to Robert Lepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9428260326385498,
            "question": "What is the URL of Robert Lepage's homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9017712473869324,
            "question": "What is the address of Robert Lepage's official website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8862621784210205,
            "question": "Where can you find information about Robert Lepage online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8705635070800781,
            "question": "Is there an online presence for Robert Lepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8705452680587769,
            "question": "What is the web address associated with Robert Lepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8532005548477173,
            "question": "Where would you go to find information about Robert Lepage on the internet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8393573760986328,
            "question": "Does Robert Lepage have a personal website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.838228166103363,
            "question": "Can you access information about Robert Lepage through the internet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.804885983467102,
            "question": "How can you find out more about Robert Lepage online?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Lepage's homepage is http://www.robertlepage.com/",
            "html": "dbpedia_577_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you access information about Robert Lepage through the internet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_577_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Robert Lepage have a personal website?",
            "html": "dbpedia_577_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where would you go to find information about Robert Lepage on the internet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_577_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_577_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_577_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_577_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_577_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_577_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_577_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_577_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_577_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_577_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_577_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nNone of the provided text documents mention a homepage address for Robert Lepage.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`\n\nThe information in the documents does not support the triple \"Robert Lepage's homepage is http://www.robertlepage.com/\". In fact, one of the documents mentions Robert Lepage's official website as \"Official Website\", but it does not provide a specific URL. However, another document mentions that he has an official website (in addition to Facebook, Instagram, X, IMDb, and The Glenn Gould Foundation)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about Robert Lepage's homepage being http://www.robertlepage.com/. While the documents provide various details about Robert Lepage, such as his work and background, they do not include the specific URL for his homepage."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}